20.
I'm going to say again.
We call the Great Shed meeting.
I was a candidate for the second floor.
I'm going to.
As a head of the official characteristic, we're going to do that.
3 findings.
Master group?
Is that a double board?
Jones?
of the 20, or died 20, second of the 24th grade reading,
and obviously it's been a bit of a 24th grade reading.
Motion of the 3D.
So both, Joe's, he's definitely part of it.
Right.
But, especially often actually,
the agency has patients or clients
who will need change during the,
which given the marker.
Okay, so I'm going to get started.
I'm going to get ready to talk to the people
who's gonna say that it's accurate, but really appreciate
the time.
So, if you don't point it in at this,
for others, it may be a lot of communication.
We, at the agency, have an opportunity to apply for it.
It's one of the other great, it requires partnerships.
It is written out by the DEA,
the one who spends one day watching producers for it.
The solution to them, they want to make a PX to kind of change it.
Three, and critically, they want to provide other community.
So we can go to die for free, and do one too,
but I'm going to give us any additional computer.
Under the screen, everything has to be done with it for years.
Right.
They want to carry on this investment in communities that are affected
by pollution and climate change.
And we have put together a real proposal.
I think we're still getting quite a bit
with both cities, not that we're here.
And I want to go now at the end of the day,
there are two things that we would like from the city.
One, we need more of the true application.
And we want to do that for the application by the end of the second.
Much of the proposed activity in our application
would happen in a particular part, and in other places,
on cities property throughout the city.
I don't know.
A company or application we will have to have a significant problem
in the city, consenting that the world described
from a project application, be done on cities property.
So that's one thing, when we come back, probably sometimes
that the world can't completely exist.
I think we're going to ask.
The second item is not so much a need,
but a strong one to greatly enhance this item.
application and that is a resolution from city council supporting the object.
We had a template, and we had a template, and we had an award, and we had a few
value.
What did you tell you?
You want out of that.
And again, the rest of that, I just wanted to jump to the end.
So today I want to over what we are hoping to do.
So, these are, I should say, these slides are important part of the story.
So, EPA is wanting to level up playing field, which we've been here these
have a lot of resources.
I can join in communities like ours that have far fewer resources.
I can join in.
And what you're doing that is by saying, hey, if you want to technical assistance
to help put together a strong application to apply.
We applauded, and we were awarded $200,000.
None of that.
But $200,000 paid to a team of late state designers,
who came to my apartment for 12 months.
They visited the tour of the area.
They met with the principal groups.
And at the second time, they came back in, after that very short
reception.
They went back to Louisiana.
And they prepared these proposals.
These design proposals.
These are conceptual designs.
These are not engineering designs.
What we also want to do is sort of a book.
But they made these.
They bought them back.
They met with folks from the city, folks from the county, from what can go
people.
And they said, okay, what can't be done?
What's hard?
What's easy?
Show us the barriers.
They're going to go back and they make a lot of reviews.
So, these will, they're going to help us have a level of playing.
A bit from much bigger communities.
Part.
So, existing folks in the United States economy, know where they are.
And they said, okay, that.
This was a smaller version.
Here's what we want to do.
We want to help the city.
Do two things.
One.
Make it a new part or manual in terms of maintenance.
Something that is easy for the city to maintain.
Two.
To make it the greatest possible community asset it can be.
What we don't have anywhere in the United States is a place to get into nature that doesn't
be all the manufacturers in the park.
If you want to go for a height, then you directly go up to cold creek or we head out on the
highway 10 towards the three line that you see.
I think you walk there.
Other way, we'll be all the time.
We'll be a driver.
We have a great deal of way in the neighborhood park.
And we'd like to try to talk to us very little trails.
If you change from year to year, we have six.
private nations and used to be manned builders, built some manned,
have more strength across the river, where there is a horse farm, but there are
like horses, have trains going through the waters, right?
But also making improvements to the ocean river.
Like this period was built between the ocean river and topry.
We can't say we go to topry, but maybe you can bring ourselves back to the
ocean river as the enhanced source of recognition for our community.
Right?
To that end, we want making improvements to the river.
We want to see why it's the bank, so it does a road away.
We want to make some ledges down to improve access for our vision for both
to go on a sit, have a picnic, right?
A long time ago, we would like to make improvements to the two buildings.
And tie-up wall, right?
Really make the river part of our community to move on.
So all that is what we hope to do with the river we part of connecting in the rail
to the ocean river.
It has the money for it, really.
So of course, the back side of the park.
So that's the one piece, right?
Hand in love with that is the city of swimming pool.
We all know it's on the slide.
We're $20 million.
The maximum ladder under the screen.
We really have strong application.
We want to help the city develop plans for an expanded water center next to the
Splash Head.
And it is our hope to be able to build the beginning of that, right?
Build a lack of a little bit there.
So that we can reclaim the swimming pool and incorporate that space into this
re-banding a river pool.
Now the second piece of this planet, public platform.
Just because I'm going to rent rates of what that land pool.
So the energy is set to set this as well.
Feel it like.
Head and you'll go, okay.
One place.
The other place.
And then of course, Splash Head.
Light-trips, they want folks who do wide-bytes because they have to.
There are some folks who buy bikes because they choose to go.
They also want people who walk.
And we would like to make that safer to make it easier to get from place to place without
having to use a vehicle, right?
We would not still be able to all of the red lines on this image.
But we believe that we can solve the most special event in river park to the Splash Head.
So the folks who go from one place to the other would have to be able to.
and our potential is that we are going to build a best-grade bridge across the country.
Right?
Uh, that's good.
Okay.
Last piece.
We don't have signs that tell the story about coming into the year.
Right?
You go to other communities and you do see a lot of signage that tells important parts of the community's story.
And we already have the agency handled five year agreement with the community.
With the National Park Service to provide the agency with technical assistance to make signage of various times.
And they already know that this way.
They are on board with helping us make really high quality signage.
And what make those signs be backed?
Right?
Well, one, our history.
We have a lot of history here.
If you go on some global-based world groups, you'll see people really celebrate that.
Well, let's bring that out into the community.
Let's have a sign at the end of the story of that dress.
Right?
Maybe I even know what you're going to do.
But it's there.
What many of us are going to do.
Right?
But also our cultures and our communities that history of mining here, the stories of farmers.
Many farmers who are here and have stories to tell their part of our community.
Those to be present, including a man, the man who is in the river of art.
Right?
A man who is a signage there that tells the story and building from there of perspective.
And also our ecology, plants and animals that we have here.
Right?
The nature that we have.
And lastly, the contamination.
Right?
We hear about that whole talk.
From the entire county, there's only one permanent sign.
And we're going to say that this is a super fun sign.
And it's outside of the repository.
Exactly.
We have children swimming in public today.
We have that for a number of years behind a nursing home.
We've been building babies.
Fishing.
Plating.
We need support.
It's on a tree.
Put up.
Signing is the very much temporarily nature.
We've been ripped up.
They get thrown away.
We don't want to clash with the community.
We would sometimes, and they just don't go into nature or fall from it.
But we do need something a little dark.
We don't sit in the property.
They say, well, don't swim in this water.
Here's one.
And with this grant, we can do all of these things.
And we involve the community in making all of these things.
It can be something that we may for ourselves.
And it's a great opportunity.
We would really love to have this.
We would have this support in this.
To be able to put it on our application.
That we have permission to do this work.
To be able to include resolution expressing this.
It's support.
So.
We would love to entertain questions, comments and I want to give back a chance I know we have a couple things we love to share it's well
So we're asking questions now really
My first question is we just have the same presentation July 1st. Why were you saying it's not going to be tell me well, I could have made just each one
So why are you doing
It's one we now know what change actually right well one one change is that
Before we were asking until the city to be a snacks for a partner, which is term of our own
It's great so every application has to be between an nonprofit organization and a statutory partner
And because of time constraints and the disease held it's played
The county auto county has joined all of us to the applicant. We are now a statutory partner in that
In principle, we don't need cities except for a partner. You know being the city as a statutory partner. So I mean
Exactly, so there was the same
Well
Because we can bring 20 million dollars to this right now
This is something that
Especially the county right
No because
They don't think it paid money
Yes, I mean, yeah, I mean they get higher person the person to make it for not interested
It's weird to deal whenever you can spot that we've got it with cater and Russell girls
We've got people are just a couple of little things that
Yep, and just those Russell family pictures are hey, I'm a man just because I was there now and we can handle it
That do any projects and go in that way
If we're looking for any deals discount with not those
That's fair. So let me tell you the hours of that very same total
Okay, we were here to ask it for action from the city to be a statutory partner
Can't believe I am happy that we can't turn it on
But the county brought it candidly, is speed.
They were faster than this general could be.
And that's not at all.
I'm not playing you.
I'm not dealing with any individual person here.
Because of that.
But these plans are being issued on a polling basis.
Every day, we didn't have a statutory worker.
Was another day, we could not get white
and application that is customized
to the person who is applying.
Right?
Was it going to be a city?
Was it going to be a capital?
We have so much willing to write this great application
for us.
I'm telling you this.
We're at the night.
We do not have a capacity to write this application
at the point.
This is being offered to us.
We had that all in one condition.
No dragon inns without a sign of worship
of the remaining supporting the application.
This is not what you love.
This is that the job done in time, so that we can receive
from the only dollars of this somebody.
And I don't care who can make this improvement of our community.
I don't care if this is the need.
I don't care if it's the hell.
What I care about is that we get it for the people.
You know, that there's still a lot of you left for us.
So, what have you done with the city?
You tried to answer that.
I've struggled with it.
I've been warning all the times.
I've been, Kevin, from the parks department.
All the times we can have meetings.
We've been trying to collect the addition to this actual apartment.
Collaborating it is which we're back and I've done entirely on our own.
The county hasn't done it.
The city hasn't done it.
We have done it.
His back.
That's what it is.
The strength of this application.
To hell.
Coax likely.
The county extension of us.
The state.
Conservation.
Congress.
To hell.
Anyway, in college.
We don't slaughter.
All of them who are all excited.
All the age, ready to go to you need two sentences of how they're going to contribute.
This project that we can put in the application.
If without a map.
They don't get anything from the town.
They don't get any assistance to contribute to this project.
All that has to be done.
In order to turn into this very large, very complicated application.
So why can we switch to the county?
We switch to the county?
We switch to the county because they can just get it done in the time frame.
We need it done.
This community.
We're going to get this out.
This is not how close the world is.
It's not about.
Cruise friendly.
Cruise going up.
What can I just.
I know.
Okay.
If you had done it first.
I would be the one.
Hello?
I'm going to be celebrating with you, but honestly, it just didn't happen.
It wasn't able to move through the process, actually.
But how many needs every single week?
You need first one days, third one day, and third one day on that one day.
Other one, I'm going to be in a special meeting, right?
Which is not something that I want to ask for, but if it didn't happen, I wouldn't take it.
I just want to see something good happen for this community.
If there's something good for this community, but I don't know what you should get the expenses.
Right.
Right, and I would also add that we are here in the business of doing things the right way,
and that takes a little bit of time, and that's what it takes.
I'm not saying you're doing it the wrong way.
You work really the right way, and I appreciate that.
Right.
So much so that you can do it to a different agency to see if you can get another passion.
Because we call special meetings all the time.
We call it the last week because we have a presentation.
So I don't know who told you, we don't need special meetings.
No, no.
You don't want to do that.
I'm not saying no, I didn't mean to suggest you don't.
These screens are very competitive.
Okay, they are very competitive.
The money is the only one.
It's the only one.
It's the last $20 million that's handed out.
August, 30, and if you have our application ready, September 1st, that's what we want.
And we don't know where the money is going to go.
What we do know is this, for your six months, right, we know it's the end of November last year.
For the first, until April, no plans to go on board, they need to get all the applications.
Right?
But then, out of them, they know.
First, large amount of grants were reported.
And if you are technical assistance, we have some information from through them about how
the case of applications are going to go and what they're doing from EDA, who is administering
grants.
And the word was, after the first round, grades, no awarded, the case of applications picked up
dramatically.
Okay?
Yeah, we could wait until the end of October to turn into grant application.
We could do that.
We could take our time and hope for the best.
But wishing, while hand spin in the other and see which one fills up for us, I didn't want
we didn't want to put ourselves in the possession of doing all this matter and missing out on
the future of two weeks longer than we could have.
It was just a matter of time.
So, you should have started to recently?
So, can I start with this process?
Okay.
Day and night.
I think you're doing the number of things that you're going to tell us that.
I've already told you that this is your order like that.
We've got to get in the bus.
We've got to know.
They're mad at us.
So just saying that I'm just the one who doesn't speak for the council.
No, of course not.
But.
There's no party.
You guys don't speak.
No, they're just in.
Okay.
When I said a surprise to the committee, Mr. Vee, I was going to go shop.
I mean, I didn't reject.
I didn't.
I can speak.
I mean, I didn't reject.
I didn't.
You know, I didn't.
You're going to.
Right.
Okay.
We all have hard times.
And sometimes we would break.
Sometimes we go.
I felt good.
I mean, I didn't.
I didn't.
I didn't get that.
So.
If that's.
I didn't.
I didn't get it back.
So when did the council start,
Probably about five days.
I think he's built a war, you folks came to the city to the county of New Jersey, right?
Then I'm not at war.
So when you tell me we've found out, I've got a commissioner, and you know I've made that decision before they didn't go to jail for it.
No, it's okay.
So if you say what I wanted to be, it's not working on it.
And they actually have to go to jail for about a minute, because they want to hear a way outside.
They don't, they did go to jail for their own land.
And they can withdraw at any time.
If you folks don't want the argument, if you want to say no, this can't happen at all.
Then they can withdraw.
They're just reaching the end of the country.
What I'm going to like to say about it, is that we all have challenges.
The city has challenges in the county, has challenges.
It has been mindful to try and pursue an opportunity that makes life more very close to a little bit better.
That creating something that we have never had, that's positive, that is spoken to everyone, that we can all enjoy.
And I believe that this project has been this project.
don't say that. And I do, of course, a sense of responsibility. To check early this period of
meeting happened, the first thing that happened in the application, for early. In the quick
this way that I can, so that we don't wind up, what it means, all kinds of work, whether it's you,
whether it's the county. And then feel like we had the blood written down from our feet, because
we were weak to light. Okay. Let's go. I'll leave. Go, Rhiner. I said, Rhiner, we need to light.
We're going to write it up from our heartbeat. We didn't know that we showed it to the medium.
A week ago that now we're going to have to get started, start a process before leaving me from that.
So Dr. Rick Rodriguez, that the others. I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know, let's go. Let's go. Let's just move on.
And I mean, I've went down to the advantage and said, we want to help the city. It's city property.
We need a city resolution to support. I said, we want to be a city community athlete. It's all about the city
until it becomes the foundation. And now they go somewhere else. We want to be a part of it. We
want to be a part of it. We need you, big, big partner. And not to get past us without us, without us, no.
Then in my veins, sir, if I'm made a souvenir, offer an observation. I'm an attempt to call every member
of this piece of all the designated cell phones. And I never want to reach a person. Okay? How do I
contact each of these at four o'clock on Friday? I didn't have a personal cell phone. I have a number
of someone by the side. Well, we all have emails. If you mean, you come to every need. You say it's every need.
You know, my personal cell phone number. I like it. So I think now we can have patrols on Friday,
so it doesn't matter. And then it should be very good. I didn't. I mean, I should not.
Okay. And I apologize, I will close. And not only that you have to necessarily know, that's
what that cell phone number is, I don't know, I don't know. I don't know what kind of cell phone number.
That I require that it was the amount of cell phone number that we receive on these phones is unprecedented.
Now I'm interested in it. So it's in good effect that we would ask this up a month.
No, I haven't. And folks, I apologize, okay? I apologize. I apologize. I will. One of the things that I
don't have to do is this.
You know, the city was this is right up just for context. This was going down back at the time
exactly
The city manager had press release about
I don't think I don't know
This is a
I don't know about our social boards. My point my point is that it is clear to me
the city had some very serious issues
on its own that could not ensure not be talking back to her. I don't expect that.
I was attempted to be pretty slow. It's time to not be down to people.
I was trying to be respectful of the process and to recognize that you have some
council meetings when you have the to hear not conduct business outside the city council
and it was mine. Perhaps mistakenly that I should not reach out to attempt to conduct
this business of the city outside the city council meeting in one of these two cities of
or one
I don't say a lot but I've done
I'm asking you to stop.
We have very serious issues in every day and we have some of the best employees that are there
in the city council meeting.
I think I think we will try to say yourself here and try to know where everybody is done.
So, you have anything to say?
Thank you very much for the time being here.
And I appreciate the possibility that we had with this grant.
I personally know that there was that there could be really a problem with accountability.
I know I can hear that there was that kind of feeling.
To me, it can even make the project stronger.
To have can take this up to the course.
You have it for no reason.
But how to do everything we want to do, we're going to hurt you because of litigation issues with
telling you, then we could plan using the county to make this corridor make you a fine way to
enjoy the practice much as we're allowed to do artwork, GRDA, with a lot of that way in the
condition, who you're going to, and we can't go to return in an application that starts making us
clear. We will want something for you. Last is my life here, and it will be a blessing for us to
occur, the river food, and the given life again. And I would love to see the corridor that takes
more people there in a way that we can all enjoy. The roof between seeing the county and the county
and my death, that would be a thing. I don't this would be really a relief, and I have to hang with
that much money. I like to say, I don't think the river food in the county is in the rivers, how this
was made, the clean, and the area is good. So I appreciate the possibility, and we will
proceed if you want us to, none of the project could happen without the city's approval, and that's how
we're going to do that. I think we had great people to make this happen, this is the
thing that's vast, the county is getting, and we need to have special people to make that happen.
We'll do that. And because in a picture like we don't want to be a partner, and that's not true.
And I don't think it's possible. I'm just saying that it's unfair that this is going to be a
institution often where we become a bad person. We become the negative piece of the equation
when we didn't realize sometimes who are part of the problem. I just want to want to make it to say that we,
the city council, and I can see for them, and I say, one of what's best is to come up. I know what to do.
So, however we can proceed behind you. Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you. Let's go offline to the U.S.E.U.G. and play.
the resolution support.
And a little bit, maybe you turn on the application.
What?
That's a green one.
We need to go with the application.
OK.
So what are we going to do?
We have to do this grant.
If I tell you, why I'm going to suggest is
if there's a willingness.
Let's sit down with you and with happy.
And let's just actually figure it out together.
Right.
Because I think we can't do that.
We're like, I mean, I don't have the right one.
It's whether it's a city we can have to do.
But we just need to get, you know, we need to be able to get this grant.
And I'm very concerned about how I'm going to display it.
When you want to turn it in by.
On the end of the second one.
Would be I do?
All right.
Would you have done that?
Yeah.
I think it could sit down.
We would just need to see the resolution.
We need to detail the background.
I mean, I know the detail.
In the application.
If you never got those before.
We have a set of meetings in this moment.
We have meetings on day.
We have one.
I'll set here with the second.
We have three meetings.
But I think you need to start.
So.
It might be better.
The record.
Well, you know, special, we are.
What needs to be done by the month,
is the application needs to be actually forbidden.
Here is what you can do.
Type it to our city council, our city manager.
And let him know over.
And then he can bring you to the city council.
Not to say.
Thank you.
For six.
The whole thing will happen.
Ben.
Okay.
We'll take it.
I'm five.
We're going to go on a six resolution.
CC 2020.
Four.
That's zero.
Six.
It's important.
Dean.
For this.
So this is the requirement.
We can say that we can turn it.
Everybody's.
We just have to have a resolution.
That's not the city.
It's in support of the mainstream program.
Which I'll be saying.
The other.
You know.
That.
The.
They.
I.
These don't.
Collect.
They.
We must come.
Thank you.
We're going to have an extra email question for the third or third or third place, the fourth or fourth place,
but allow us with a very young, or early childhood care, to make it one way street, very school hours.
God, it's in Gowey.
I was approached by Gowey.
I'll get this kind of started.
This is actually going to be, you know, it's got to be cold.
It's going to be, you know, it's got to be cold, it's going to be cold.
And the answer, I wanted this one.
For the second one, the fourth and then the fourth and then the fourth and then the second one,
each side of the school is going to be out of the contract.
One line.
What was it?
It's going to be on the next street there.
Pointing towards the third and the third, the third one's out.
What should we look for?
Second.
We've got one.
Five.
Two.
Three.
One.
Make sure the first goes next.
Thank you.
America means, Lee's a part of the link that lives on.
That we allón, degrees about our judge.
Then we'll try to get three days of the meal.
No worries, thank you so much for yourHOP.
Thank you.
Thank you also much.
Two.
No.
Then, of course.
And there are some radioqueen, big a copy of the officer manager.
Or as an Eつan,
Excutif Nancy.
Second.
One.
We got two.
Nice.
It's a jam, isn't it?
You're going to be able to hear it.
Hold on.
One of the things we talk about.
This area is, you have to update a deck.
You're not going to waste three minutes of spending
for your article with our event.
And this time, I'd just like to use for all of the things
you know, this is out of here.
Or you might be not going to have to prevent change
where it's at least in the additional information
as far as the hang of memory, or your programming,
all of that, probably available.
The jam has everything into that.
This is every hand of the National League 8.
That one will be viewed.
And it also a very convenient.
It wasn't paid by the touch.
So those are the main components.
So I wanted everything actually there.
The last one was root.
So, double the time, each step, Jail is a part of it.
All right, we'll go ahead.
Well, I'm going to move to the professional services
available with Barbara, but the library is on our report.
The new terminal of contact number of two to zero,
114 to zero, correct?
Good evening.
How are you?
So, the original meeting with Barbara on the air pool
for their professional services.
I don't know.
Well, we've got the largest budget.
This amendment became at 27.9.
So, we're saying for a week, that was about 27.5.
Sorry.
And Cindy, that can't provide to the members,
that have a local guarder and...
We'll be taking us on that budget.
I don't know.
We'll be asking.
Thank you.
Okay.
You guys have a thing out.
Max will take you out.
Take that pudding.
Barbara, Barbara and his crew.
They're starting on the green.
I mean, the green ones.
It looks.
And then she'll be pulling a slap.
Early next week.
We'll be next week.
I'll go home on the camera.
Thank you.
Barbara?
Black.
Double.
Is that part of Kail?
Well, there's a lot of things to read.
We're going to go to the right.
We'll be going to the right.
Okay.
And we'll be back.
13.
There's on the right.
14.
We'll be back.
Okay.
14.
That's it.
We're going to be back.
13.
15.
The special service is very open.
They just write your name and I'll give you a visit for your 24.
Let's do a proof.
13.
Another thing that is available is the list of the questions of this agenda.
17.
That works.
18.
Rare account book.
We need to be in the development.
You know, we're not just reiterating.
We do this for free.
We do the best of the candidates in the world.
We do the best of our community.
And people that try to paint picture and put us into this issue.
I think it's worth that way, really.
Push it.
This is my blood.
So I apologize if I have to tell you today, but I love my little time, little time, little
time.
You call out my integrity and we're going to talk to you all so much about that.
Thank you.
I just want to say thank you to all of our colleagues, you know, I'm pretty much going to
getting through.
I don't know if there's guys who are out for a couple of days, we're sort of power, another
another.
That's your duties, but all of those are part of part of the parts of part of the, every
part we have, and I'm just appreciate all of you for going to that action of my office.
So they don't always see it.
They don't like it's our job to make sure they know what you guys do, and how hard you work
because we can't be successful without you.
And if you guys are doing the work, so pass one of your crews and your teams that we appreciate
Josh, one of them who's been a pretty good critic in the city over the years, send me a text
question today, and actually pass on his gratitude thanks to our city elected crew, as they call
all of them as a power source really quickly, you know, call them all, make sure that everything
is good.
So guys, you're doing the right things.
And people start with others, and you're going to have a big, big screen to call them,
they say, thank you, you're winning, and if you guys win, you're going to have a city, and so
thank you.
See you later, everyone.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
All right, 66, guys, for building here, you should get full of the city.
You have four years now, that outstanding job again, once again.
20, this thing will not be really big, but a big group, a big group, a big group, a
big group.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.